http://www.acescrubs.com/privacypolicy

Shop by brands Medical (A-J)Barco OneCherokee MedicalCherokee WorkwearDanskoFundamentalsGrey's AnatomyGrey's Anatomy SignatureHeartSoulMedical (K -Z)Klogskoi Basicskoi Litekoi Next Genkoi StretchLandauMetaNurse MatesTherafirmTooniformsWonderWinkZoe+Chloe ProfessionalCarharttChef WorksChefwearPort AuthorityUncommon Threads FootwearDanskoKlogsShop by Products MedicalBottomsScrub SetsHospitalityBottomsHeadwearSpecial Offers Learn About Us
Welcome
Thanks for visiting AceScrubs.com. We want to be your supplier of medical uniforms, footwear and equipment! AceScrubs.com is a division of Ace Uniforms in San Diego. Since 1958, Ace Uniforms has supplied public safety professionals, medical personnel and others with all of their uniform needs for head to toe. Our 50 years of experience demonstrates our commitment to customer service.
We carry scrubs, lab coats, jackets, shoes and more for medical professionals from leading suppliers such as Dickies, koi, Barco, Cherokee, Landau, Dansko, Klogs, Littman, Prestige and more. . We carry a variety of stethoscopes, Sphygmomanometer Sets, watches, Tunable Diaphragm and many more required accessories for your work environment. Besides outfitting the nursing and doctors of the world, we also provide the uniform needs for auxiliary, volunteers, engineering, hospitality, housekeeping, food services and all departments for your facility.
Our selection includes medical uniforms that provide comfort and a great appearance for your everyday wear! Ace Uniforms believes in providing "Scrubs that you want to wear 12 hours a day."
Remember that we can embroider any piece of clothing or accessory that you buy from us.
We add merchandise continuously, so check back often.
Ace Uniforms
REquestpreferred groups
Privacy Policy
Ace Scrubs take the privacy of your personal information seriously. This Internet Privacy Policy describes the measures we take to help ensure the security of information collected through our Web sites.
How Personal Information is Collected and Used
We only collects personal information that you voluntarily submit through our Web sites. This may include information such as your name, street and e-mail addresses, and telephone number. We do not automatically collect personal information without your knowledge.
Uses of Personal Information
When you submit personal information to us, you will be asked to decide how we may use your information. Unless we specifically tell you otherwise before you submit personal information, we will only use it to:
Respond to your questions or comments
Better understand your purchasing habits and needs
Help us understand how we can improve our products, services, and Web site
Inform you about special promotions
Contact you to ask for your opinion or willingness to participate in certain events
Limiting the Use of Your Information
If you submit personal information to us, you have two options:
You may choose to allow us to use the personal information for any of the purposes described under the "Uses of Personal Information" section of our Privacy Policy. This is called the "Opt-In" choice.
You may choose to restrict our use of your information to a specific application, such as answering your question about a product. This is called the "Opt-Out" choice.
These options give you the opportunity to control the usage of your personal information by "opting out" of our systems.
Use of Cookies
To improve your visit to our sites, we may use "cookies" to obtain non-personal information (cookies are text information files that your browser places on your computer when you visit a Web site). We may aggregate this data to analyze the viewing habits of our site visitors, but it will not be associated with any personally identifiable data.
Sharing Your Personal Information With Others
We will not use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to the uses described above unless we provide you with prior notice and give you an opportunity to change your usage preferences.Unless you give us prior consent, we will not trade, sell, or share your personal information with any person or entity other than
Ace Uniforms, our affiliates and representatives, unless required by law or as disclosed to you before the information is collected.For certain promotions or product requests, we may share your information with an outside company for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order. These companies are carefully selected by us and also take the protection of your personal information seriously.
Access to Your Information
To modify your personal information, contact us at
info@aceuniforms.com We will make every effort to respond to your requests in a timely manner.If you have already submitted personal information to acescrubs.com, you may opt-out of the company's future use of that information by sending an e-mail to info@aceuniforms.com. Upon receiving your request, we will delete your personal information from our records.
Security of Your Information
The security of your personal information is very important to us. We use appropriate technical and managerial procedures to protect your personal information and prevent its disclosure outside of us. Only those authorized by us will be granted access to your personal information.In addition to careful consideration about what information you share and who you share it with, we recommend that everyone develop good security habits. These include protecting and regularly changing your password, using computer virus protection, logging off when you finish using your computer, and considering the use of file or email encryption programs.
E-mail Preferences
acescrubs.com offers you the opportunity to choose whether or not you prefer to receive marketing materials via e-mail by sending us notice at
info@aceuniforms.com. You may update this preference at any time. Please allow us sufficient time to process your change of preference.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may amend this Internet Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check back for updates.
